# Luding Andrés Castañeda García Software Developer



#### **Contact**

✓ <u>ludingnumpaque@gmail.com</u>

+573193760301

in <u>Luding Castañeda</u>

#### Skills

#### **Backend technologies**

Python (Flask)

Ruby (Rails)

Js JavaScript (Express)

**-co** Go (Fiber)

#### Frontend technologies

5 Html, Css and JS

Js JavaScript (VueJS, ReactJS)

#### Other technologies

Docker (CI/CD)

Git (Github)

#### **Soft Skills**

Leadership

**2)** Communication

Planning

Agile methodologies (Scrum)

## **Profile**

I'm a passionate Software Developer with experience working in the Web World, I really love work with new technologies and create creative solutions for problems using software as a tool. Usually I learn about innovation by testing Machine learning models or making mechanics in video games engines (commonly Godot), is part of my aventure spirit.

## **Professional Experience**

## **Full-Stack Developer**

Fusepong (Sep 2021 - Present)

I'm making new developments with a great team as full-stack developer using PostgreSQL and Rails in the backend and, VueJS with Cordova in frontend. Additionally, we use Docker with different frameworks, usually from Python for create operative systems in micro-controllers and microservices connected with CI/CD in Kubernetes with Github Actions. All focused on create an integrated ecosystem of innovation in Latam access control and security.

## **Web Developer**

Freelance (Jul 2019-Sep 2021)

Worked on a lot of independent or personal projects with MERN stack (MoogoDB, Express, ReactJS, Node), using in some cases Handlebars like template motor (for fast projects without a big frontend requirement).

## **Education**

## **Electronic Engineering**

<u>UNAD</u> (Universidad Nacional Abierta y a Distancia) 2021 - Present

I'm studying Electronic Engineering, I've learned C, C++ and VHDL focused in the implementation of micro-controllers and micro-processors, also I'm learning the process to design intermediate level integrated circuits for build simple electronic machines by myself.

# Technical Degree in Software Development SENA (Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje) 2019 - 2021

Basis of software development from logic to advance algorism and OOP are concepts that I learned in this institute, coding in Java and PHP and building personal web apps.